If there's one thing worse than dying and going to
Hell, it's not dying - and going to Hell.
Highway to Hell is a fantasy, action, comedy film directed by Ate de Jong.
Charlie and Rachel run away from home to get married in Las Vegas.
But they get attacked by a zombie who takes Rachel with him to
hell, where she will become one of Satan's brides
Beezle, played by Patrick Bergin.
Royce, played by Adam Storke.
Charlie Sykes, played by Chad Lowe.
Rachel Clark, played by Kristy Swanson.
Clara, played by Pamela Gidley.
Adam, played by Jarrett Lennon.
Highway to Hell is a 1992 American B horror comedy film directed by Ate de
Jong and starring Chad Lowe, Kristy Swanson and Patrick Bergin.
It was written by Brian Helgeland.
The film tells the story of Charlie Sykes (Lowe) and his girlfriend Rachel Clark (Swanson), who is kidnapped by a demon and
taken to Hell to become one of Satan's brides, while Charlie must travel to the other dimension to rescue her.
The film features cameo appearances by Lita Ford, Gilbert Gottfried, actor Ben Stiller,
his sister Amy Stiller and their parents, Jerry Stiller and Anne Meara.
In 2019, Gottfried reprised his role as Adolf Hitler from the film
in the comedy television series Historical Roasts.
The film explores themes of rescue, virgin, police, hell, highway.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.